



Ferhat Adıbelli

Date of birth: 15/11/1991 | **Nationality:** Turkish | **Gender:** Male

Phone number: (+90) 5459433435 (Mobile) | Email address:

<u>ferhatadibelli9@gmail.com</u> | **Website:** <u>https://ferhatadibelli0.github.io/Portfolio/</u>

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/ferhatadibelli9/ | Stackoverflow:

https://stackoverflow.com/users/19093788/ferhat-adibelli | **Github:**

https://github.com/FerhatAdibelli0

Address: Gazeteci Hasan Tahsin Cad., No:77, Karabağlar, 35150, İzmir, Türkiye (Home)

ABOUT ME

I'm Ferhat. I am from Turkey, I live in Turkey. As a FullStack Developer, I`m very passionate and talented about ReactJS (Redux), React Native, NextJS, Typescript, NodeJS, ExpressJS, NestJS, MongoDB, Redis, Nginx, MySQL, PostgreSQL, Docker, Docker Swarm, Kubernetes and AWS. I devoted myself to learning, implementing, adapting, and creating throughout my life to build intelligent web apps to help people and improve life quality around the world. As a Web Developer with 2 years of experience able to build web applications from the ground up - information gathering, planning, design, development, testing and delivery, and maintenance.

WORK EXPERIENCE

01/06/2022 - CURRENT İstanbul, Türkiye

FULLSTACK DEVELOPER CODEVENTURE AŞ

I have worked as a full-stack developer at Codeventure company, contributing to numerous projects. Some of the key projects I have been involved in include Vimesoft Chat Application, El Poder Del Amour, Hangicheckup.com, and Microfon.co. In these projects, I utilized advanced technologies such as socket.io, web socket, webRTC, Payload CMS. Additionally, I managed container orchestration processes using Docker Swarm.

02/2022 - 05/2022 Türkiye

FRONTEND DEVELOPER ALME TECH

Building user interfaces for websites and/or web applications Working with ReactJS, Redux, TypeScript Creating self-contained, reusable, and testable modules and components Writing some end-to-end test on JestJS

01/2021 - 01/2022 Türkiye

FREELANCER UPWORK

Upwork helped me find my first job as a FullStack Developer. It allows me to focus on what is most important for my clients - product and project development.

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

2010 - 2014

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE Turkish Military Academy - Ankara

Field of study Industrial and Systems Engineering | Final grade 3.65/4

Field of study Computer Forensic

DIGITAL SKILLS

React ecosystem: ReactJS, React Router, Redux, Typescript | Backend: NodeJS, Express, socket.io | NestJS Framework | Unit Testing | Microservices with Nodejs | WebRTC native API | Google Maps, GPS Tracking | RESTful api | Web Socket | graphQL | nextjs | FireBase | Object-Oriented Programming | Sequelize and Mongoose | Git/Gitlab/GitHub | MySQL, SQL, SQLite, PostgreSQL | Mongodb / Mongoose | Supabase | End-to-end tests | Platform: AWS Cloud | Good understanding of Kubernetes | Docker & Docker Swarm | React-React Native | GitLab CICD | GitHub Actions | NATS and NATS Streaming

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

HONOURS AND AWARDS

ReactJS -- The Complete Guide - Academind

Link https://drive.google.com/file/d/1UPC_WHLoWUOf9ADO-6JEahHS7nlzeJb0/view?usp=sharing

ReactJS -- Web Programming - BTK Academy

Link https://drive.google.com/file/d/1GIUX8brBrknCW8iVHf1Wg_CLPz_g7vMr/view?usp=sharing

NodeJS -- The Complete Guide - Academind

Link https://drive.google.com/file/d/1QxMxt8Wh-j9NF83Sqqsbr8l3E6rRcaqK/view?usp=sharing

Advanced Nodels Concept - Stephen Grider

Link https://udemy-certificate.s3.amazonaws.com/image/UC-189a7088-28e4-4ec3-ba82-85531e362196.jpg

MongoDB- The Complete Developer Guide - Academind

Link https://udemy-certificate.s3.amazonaws.com/image/UC-7991e721-c8d0-4b86-99cf-f4bd5b0a3e60.jpg

Microservices with NodeJS - Stephen Grider

Link https://www.udemy.com/certificate/UC-ac2267d8-75a3-4d73-875e-1461f74e81d5/

Redis -The Complete Developer Guide - Stephen Grider

Link https://udemy-certificate.s3.amazonaws.com/image/UC-2ba5688a-c1de-403d-b1d8-3fdfae77274e.jpg

Docker & Kubernetes - Academind

Link https://udemy-certificate.s3.amazonaws.com/image/UC-e4d3fdcc-32f1-4325-9ccf-b49e46c2389d.jpg

React Native - The Practical Guide - Academind

Link https://udemy-certificate.s3.amazonaws.com/image/UC-e21d1585-902a-4db9-bcac-e52ecb5db62d.jpg

Language Competency - American Culture School

Link https://drive.google.com/file/d/1HOzdEH-8ytlH_u9XtqXbyaSJIGwNmwDa/view?usp=sharing

AWS Essentials - Academind

Link https://udemy-certificate.s3.amazonaws.com/image/UC-01d6b0ae-3d4a-4e40-8330-14a52af0263f.jpg

Microfrontend with React - Stephen Grider

Link https://www.udemy.com/certificate/UC-d6724ec6-f097-4fe9-9bd3-489333a6e474/

